There is deception [music] and desire too
I am saying this to myself inside
Still I am innocent I am innocent I am innocent I am
innocent what I am
[music] not There were
one or two people who are just looking straight at you
Krystal is looking a bit changed so
my doubt is a bit high there
Why are you avoiding my gaze I will
try to see your expressions [music] Moderator are
you crazy
friend Till now I am
feeling the same about Krystal whatever you just said to me [music]
Karan Singh
will believe the magics then no one will doubt us.
Create Karan Singh Magic as Karan Singh Tragic with your gentle hands.
Last night traitors murdered Karan [Music] Parda Parda
Yes Parda Parda Yes What kind of a veil from loved ones
[Music] Parda Yes Parda Parda Yes
What kind of a veil from loved ones